Guide to the Cornell University Chorus Records, 1917-2016
Cornell University Chorus Records, 1917-2016
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Cornell University Chorus records, 1917-2016
14-20-3125
Cornell University Chorus
4.4 cubic ft.
Correspondence, photographs, cassette tapes, broadsides, programs, video tapes, awards.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Correspondence, sound and video recordings, miscellany documenting the Cornell University Chorus.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Collection includes correspondence, photographs, cassette tapes, broadsides, programs, video tapes, and awards of the Cornell University Chorus.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Cornell University--Students.
Subjects:
Choirs.; Concert programs--New York (State)--Ithaca.; Music.
Form and Genre Terms:
Programs.; Broadsides.; Videotapes.; Photographs.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Cassette: Cornell Trustee Weekend Choral Concert, 1983; tr-10129 (Box 1)
- Cassette: Cornell Fall Concert, 1983; tr-10130 (Box 1)
- Cassette: November, Music of Bohuslav Martinu, November 19, 1984; tr-10131 (Box 1)
- Cassette: Verdi Requiem, March, March 3, 1985; tr-10132 (Box 1)
- Cassette: April, Spring Concert, April 19, 1986; tr-10133 (Box 1)
- Cassette: November, Fall Concert, November 15, 1986; tr-10134 (Box 1)
- Cassette: November, November 13, 1987; tr-10135 (Box 1)
- Cassette: Performance Selections, 1988-89; tr-10136 (Box 1)
- Cassette: April, April 8, 1988; tr-10137 (Box 1)
- Cassette: Chorus Selections, 1988-1989; tr-10138 (Box 1)
- Cassette: November, November 18, 1988; tr-10139 (Box 1)
- Cassette: CBS Radio Broadcast December, December 1988; tr-10140 (Box 1)
- Cassette: CBS Cavalcade of Christmas Music, 1989; tr-10141 (Box 1)
- Cassette: April, April 22, 1989; tr-10142 (Box 1)
- Cassette: October, October 21, 1989; tr-10143 (Box 1)
- Cassette: Twilight Concert, November 3, 1990; tr-10144 (Box 1)
- Cassette: Twilight Concert, November 3, 1990; tr-10145 (Box 1)
- Cassette: November, November 2, 1991; tr-10146 (Box 1)
- Cassette: November, November 2, 1991; tr-10147 (Box 1)
- Cassette: November, November 2, 1991; tr-10148 (Box 1)
- Cassette: Performance Selections, 1991-1992; tr-10149 (Box 1)
- Cassette: Chorus Tour, 1993; tr-10150 (Box 1)
- Cassette: Senior Week Concert, May 29, 1993; tr-10151 (Box 1)
- Cassette: Twilight Fall Concert, November 4, 1995; tr-10152 (Box 1)
- Digital Audio Tape: Star Spangled Banner, February 2, 1996; tr-10153 (Box 1)
- Cassette: Cornell University Chorus and Glee Club present Brahm's ein deutches Requiem, February 4, 1996; tr-10154 (Box 1)
- Cassette: The Cornell University Glee Club and Chorus, Senior Week Concert 1997, May 24, 1997; tr-10155 (Box 1)
- Cassette: unmarked tape, n.d.; tr-10156 (Box 1)
- Video Tape: Chorus Rehearsal Sage Chapel, October 21, 1989; V-7077 (Box 1)
- Video Tape: MacNeil/Lehrer Report: Susan Davenny-Wyner, V-7078 (Box 1)
- Video Tape: Lift the Chorus, n.d.; V-7079 (Box 1)
- Magnetic Tape: BRNO Choir at Cornell University, April 26, 1972; tr-10126 (Box 1)
- Magnetic Tape: Cornell Chorus Fall Concert, November 13, 1982; tr-10127 (Box 1)
- Magnetic Tape: Cornell Chorus, November 19, 1983; tr-10128 (Box 1)
- Archives Guest Book, n.d. (Box 1)
- Photo: Student Chorus Group Picture, 1943 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Photo: "The Town Hall" Pamphlet, 1943 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Group photo, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Group photos, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Group photos, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Group photos, 1982-1987 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Group photos, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Group photos, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Group photos, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Group photos, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Group photos, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Group photos, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Miscellaneous Negatives, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Cornell University Chorus Picture Album: Misc. Photos through Phon-a-Thon, Spring 1999, n.d.-1999 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Singing Gram: Singing Strait Cookies, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Singing Gram: Singing Valentines, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Singing Gram: Cookie Break Music, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Alumni Correspondence: Alumnae Lists, Notes, Cards, Postcards (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Alumnae Letters, 1979-80 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Social: Paperwork, invitations and information about social events (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Attendance Rosters, 1980s-1990s (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Attendance Roster copies, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Sokol's Intro Letter and Model Thank-you letter to alumni, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Cornell Chorus Attendance policy (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Newsletters, 1980-1996 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Newsletter Rewrites/Alternative Texts and Newsletter Articles (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Annual reports: Misc. Reports, 1959-1996 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Managerial Forms and Correspondence, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Alumni Correspondence, 1981-82 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Publicity: Misc. Newspaper Clippings and Pamphlets (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Publicity: information about the group, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Financial: Misc. Financial and Donation Records (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Financial Records, 1979-early 80s (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Chorus Minutes, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Chorus Minutes, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Chorus Minutes, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Chorus Minutes, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Chorus Tour Programs, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Chorus Tour Programs, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Chorus Tour Programs, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Chorus Tour Programs, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Chorus Tour Programs, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Tour Information: Harvard, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Tour Information: Singing Straight Breaks, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Tour Information: Spring Tour, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Tour Information, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Chorus Directories, 1991-1998 (Box 3)
- Chorus Attendance Books (Box 3)
- Daily Log, 1985-89 (Box 3)
- Scarf Design, 1993 (Box 3)
- Performance History: Dates and times of Chorus Performances, 1960-1993 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Chorus Programs, 1995-1996 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Chorus Programs, 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Chorus Programs, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Chorus Programs, 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Chorus Programs, 1991-1992 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Chorus Programs, 1990-1991 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Chorus Programs, 1989-1990 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Chorus Programs, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Chorus Programs, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Chorus Programs, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Chorus Programs, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Chorus Programs, 1984-1985 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Chorus Programs, 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Chorus Programs, 1982-1983 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Chorus Programs, 1981-1982 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Chorus Programs, 1980-1981 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Chorus Programs, 1959, 1979-1980 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Membership Surveys, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Misc. Chorus Documents 1: Sopranos, 1950s (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Misc. Chorus Documents 2: Altos, 1950s (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Misc. Chorus Documents: Miscellaneous Papers, 1950-1960 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Misc. Chorus Documents 1: Miscellaneous Papers, 1960s (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Misc. Chorus Documents 2: Miscellaneous Papers, 1960s (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Misc. Chorus Documents 3: Business and Membership, 1960s (Box 4, Folder 25)
- Misc. Chorus Documents: Roll-book and Papers, 1970-1976 (Box 4, Folder 26)
- Misc. Chorus Documents 1: Publicity, Singing Strait Breaks, University Correspondence Senior Week, 1977-1981 (Box 4, Folder 27)
- Misc. Chorus Documents 2: Sponsorship, Mahler 1980, Council Meeting minutes, 1977-1981 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Misc. Chorus Documents 3: Fall 79 Trip Correspondence, Letter to returning members, Letter to incoming Freshmen, Orientation, 1977-1981 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Awards: For Participation in the 26th and 34th Annual Classic Intercollegiate Women's Glee Club Association Festival Competition (Box 5, Folder 3-4)
- Book: Songs of Cornell, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Constitution, by-Laws, annual reports, 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Programs, 1986-1995 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Programs, 1996-1999 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Programs, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Programs, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Programs, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Programs, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Tour, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Programs, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Miscellaneous documents, 1965-2003 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Correspondence, schedules, elections, 1980-2001 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Newsletters, 1992-2002 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Photographs, 1969-2001 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Alumni address information, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Alumni address information, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Notes Spring 2001-Fall 2007 [scattered issues], 2001-2007 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Programs, 2005-2014 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- Cornell University Chorus leaflets, [1996] (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Programs from China Tour, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Chorus Bios (photos), 1999-2005 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- Clippings and Chronicles, 1997-2007 (Box 5, Folder 25)
- Posters [8.5"x11"], 2008; undated (Box 5, Folder 26)
- Posters [8.5"x14"], 2006; undated (Box 5, Folder 27)
- Tickets for events, 2016 (Box 6)
- Programs, 2015-2016 (Box 5)
- Advisory Council Meeting Minutes, June 2015 (Box 5)
- Posters, 1980-2014 (Folder 1)
- Oversize items (Folder 1)
  Includes 1917 group photograph, New York State Legislative Resolution signed by Steven M. Boggess, commending the Chorus on the occasion of its Sun-Kissed Tour.